export const SportsData = [
 {
    id:0,
    question:`Who was the first African-American man to become the World Heavyweight Champion? `,
    options: [`Calvin Johnson`, `Joe Louis`, `Beyonce`, ` Jack Johnson`],
    answer: `Jack Johnson`
},
{
    id:1,
    question:`Who was the first black man to score 100 points in a basketball game? `,
    options: [`Wilt Chamberlain`, `Joe Louis`, `LeBron James`, ` Kyrie IrvingÂ `],
    answer: `Wilt Chamberlain`
},
{
    id:2,
    question:`Who was the fastest runner in the Berlin Olympics?`,
    options: [`Usain Bolt`, `Helen Stephens`, `Jesse Owens`, ` Jackie Joyner`],
    answer: `Jesse Owens`
},
{
    id:3,
    question:`Who is considered the greatest NBA star ever `,
    options: [`Chris Paul`, `Michael Jordan`, `Magic Johnson`, ` Lebron James`],
    answer: `Lebron James`
},
{
    id:4,
    question:`What team did Jackie Robinson first play on? `,
    options: [`Mississippi State`, `Los Angelos Dodgers`, `Red Sox's`, ` New York Giants`],
    answer: `Los Angelos Dodgers`
},
{
    id:5,
    question:`Serena and Venus Williams are stars in what professional sport?  `,
    options: [`basketball`, `tennis`, `soccer`, ` volleyball`],
    answer: `tennis`
},
{
    id:6,
    question:`The all-black basketball team the Harlem Globetrotters was formed in what year? `,
    options: [`1927`, ` 1938`, `1959`, ` 1970`],
    answer: `1927`
},
{
    id:7,
    question:` Stripped of his heavyweight title in 1967 for refusing induction into the U.S. military, Muhammad Ali regained the heavyweight championship on October 30, 1974, in Kinshasa, Zaire (present-day Democratic Republic of the Congo), with an eighth-round knockout of which prizefighter?  `,
    options: [`George Foreman`, `Joe Frazier`, `Leon Spinks`, ` John Lewis`],
    answer: `George Foreman`
},
{
    id:8,
    question:`  In 1957 Althea Gibson became the first African American to do what? `,
    options: [`She won the US Open tennis Championship`, `She joined the Ladies Professional Golf Association`, `She was name chairperson of the President's Council on Physical Fitness and Sports`, ` She won the WBNA Championship`],
    answer: `She won the US Open tennis Championship`
},
{
    id:9,
    question:` Star basketball player Michael Jordan led his team, the Chicago Bulls, to how many NBA World Championships in the 1990s?  `,
    options: [`Four`, `Six`, `Eight`, `Twelve`],
    answer: `Six`
},

]